http://www.sirspeedy.com/privacy-policy/

We use cookies to better understand how you use our website so that we can improve your experience. By continuing to browse or closing this banner, you indicate your agreement. To learn more, please visit our Privacy Policy.
Franchise Opportunities
Request a Quote
Send a File
Social Media
English
›English
›Arabic
›Belarusian
›Brunei
›Bulgarian
›Catalan
›Chinese (Simplified)
›Chinese (Traditional)
›Croatian
›Czech
›Danish
›Dutch
›Estonian
›Filipino
›Finnish
›French
Own A Franchise
You have unshakable ambition, a dedicated work ethic and a deep desire to succeed. Sir Speedy can help you achieve it. Independence. Unlimited growth potential. Go after your dream.
LEARN MORE
Sign In to Send a File
Connect With a Social Network
Sign in With Your Email Address
Email Address
Password
Forgot your password?
Stay Signed In
Don't have an account?
Sign Up
Not ready to sign up?
Send Files as a Guest
Sign In New Customers
Sign Up With a Social Network
Sign up with Your Email Address
Register
Not Ready to Sign Up
Sending Files is Quick and Easy
Send Files as a Guest
Products & Services
Your business challenges want solutions, and that’s what we provide.
Find the printing, signs, and marketing services you need—all right here.
VIEW ALL PRODUCTS & SERVICES
Company Info
COMPANY INFO
Decades of experience. Industry leadership. Attentive customer service. These & more define Sir Speedy Print, Signs and Marketing.
Learn More
MANAGEMENT
Don F.
Lowe
Richard
Lowe
Dan
Conger
NEWS
September 23, 2020
|
Naperville,
IL
Local Business Receives Franchise Sales Achievemen... More
August 25, 2020
|
Mission Viejo,
CA
Sir Speedy, PIP and Signal Graphics Franchisees Re... More
PARTNERS
Partner
1
Partner
2
Partner
HISTORY
Our mission for the last 50 years has been simple – provide the very best quality and service.
IN THE MEDIA
August 14, 2018
|
Graphic Display World
Sir Speedy celebrates 50-Year Anniversary More
May 14, 2018
|
What They Think? Market Intelligence for the Printing Industry
SurveyAdvantage Recognizes Top Franchise and Independent Printers More
Insights
ALL BRIEFS & WHITEPAPERS
The Direct Mail Phoenix Rises Again
Paired with the latest technology, direct mail might be your secret marketing weapon More
Maximizing Your Event Marketing ROI
By applying these best practices of integrated marketing you can take your next event from good to great. More
Getting Personal: An Introduction to One-to-One Marketing
Inbound marketing-focused organizations see a 61% lower cost-per-lead than outbound-focused companies. More
VIDEO LIBRARY
ALL CASE STUDIES
Use Mobile Marketing To Create Awareness More
Signage Helps Store Promote New Clothing Line
More
3D Signage for 55+ Living Home
More
Join Our Team
WHY WORK WITH US
WE’VE GOT HISTORY & HAPPINESS WORKING FOR US. It’s a winning formula that attracts professionals with great skills, talent and personality – just like you.
Learn More
JOB PROFILES
Customer Service Guide the customer experience.More
Graphic Design Creating and building brands.More
Sales Drive results.More
FIND A JOB
Recent Jobs
Dec 08, 2020 | Prescott, AZ.
Outside Sales
View Job
Dec 02, 2020 | Chicago, IL.
Customer Service Representative
View Job
Nov 18, 2020 | Manhattan, KS.
New Business Account Executive
View Job
“I would tell someone thinking about working at Sir Speedy, that it is an amazing place with great people.”
Start Your Job Search
Blog
ABOUT MARKETING TANGO
MarketingTango Is Your Go-To Resource On Integrated Marketing.
Want to learn more about the holistic advantages of integrated marketing? Check our blog for frequent updates on trends, marketing tactics and the do’s and don’t’s.
You’ll find postings on real-world solutions, articles, ideas and testimonials that
shed light on how businesses of all sizes can leverage the vast array of media channels available in today’s market.
Visit The Blog
RECENT POSTS
12/08/2020
Why Outsourcing Marketing is Good for Your Bottom Line
More
12/01/2020
Holiday Gifting is Different This Year. Here’s How to Do It Right
More
11/24/2020
Storytellers Are the Best New Marketers
More
MENU
Products & Services+
All
Products & Services
Franchise Opportunities
Privacy PolicyWelcome to the Sir Speedy® website available at
www.sirspeedy.com and at other uniform resource locators and the related or linked web pages of our franchised Sir Speedy Centers. In this Privacy Policy, You are referred to as "You" "Your(s)" “Yourself” or "User".
“We” and “Our” refer to Sir Speddy, Inc.
It is the policy of Sir Speedy, Inc. to respect and protect the privacy of the users of the Sites (collectively, the "Site"). Through this Privacy Policy, we want to reassure users of the Site that we will not sell, share, or rent user information to others in a manner different than as set forth in this Privacy
Policy.
1. Information Collection.
Sir Speedy, Inc. collects personally identifiable information from the users of the Site only if you voluntarily provide it to us and you have the option not to provide any personally identifiable information to us.
For example, we collect your name, email,
telephone number and other information when you subscribe to receive news and offers, access interactive features such as our whitepapers, e-newsletter or our blog, or if you use the Send-A-File or Request-A-Quote features.
If you request franchise information, we
collect your name, address, telephone number, email and other information you may wish to share about yourself. If we have trouble processing a request, this contact information may be used by Sir Speedy, Inc. to contact the user.
2. Gathering and Sharing of Information, Links to External and Co-Branded Websites. We may monitor traffic patterns on the Site and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use to analyze trends and administer the Site in order to improve its layout and design and to permit Site personalization
and streamlining to create the best Site experience we can for our users. In order to perform analysis permitting such personalization and improvement of site design and user experience, we may employ suitable third parties with whom we share the information necessary to accomplish these objectives. These
statistics include no personally identifying information.
Where appropriate, we share aggregated statistical information with our business partners. These statistics include no personally identifying information.
We may provide personal identifying and account information in special cases such as enforcement of our Terms and Conditions of Site Use, or as required by law or legal process to protect and defend the rights and safety of our Site and its users. This includes
exchanging information with other companies for purposes of fraud and credit risk reduction.
Our Site may also contains links to external Internet sites as well as co-branded sites which may be operated by an external party and which may have privacy practices that differ from those here at www.sirspeedy.com. A co-branded site is a Website, usually operated by a
third-party, and displaying that third-party's name along with the Sir Speedy name and logo. When you click on links that take you to such external or co-branded sites, you will be subject to their privacy policies, and we encourage you to become familiar with that party's privacy policies as these
may differ from those utilized on our Site. Please note that this privacy policy applies solely to information collected by Sir Speedy, Inc. on our Site and, while we strongly support the protection of privacy on the Internet, we cannot be responsible for the privacy practices of other Websites, uses of the
information collected by other Websites, or the content of those other Websites.
3.
Consent. By using our Site, the user agrees to the terms and conditions set forth in this Privacy Policy and the Site Terms and Conditions of Use INCLUDING ALL LIMITATIONS AND DISCLAIMERS PROVISIONS which are an integral part hereof, and the user consents to the collection and use of this information by Sir
Speedy, Inc. as disclosed in this Privacy Policy. We may revise this Privacy Policy or the Site Terms and Conditions of Use at any time by updating these postings. By using this Site you agree to be bound by any such revisions in effect at the time of use and should therefore periodically visit this page and the Site
Terms and Conditions of Use page to determine the then current policies applicable to users of the Site.
4.
Security Information. Strong precautions are taken to protect the information of the users of our Site. When users submit sensitive information via the Site, that Information is protected both online and off-line. Only those of our employees who need the information to perform a
specific function are granted access to personally identifiable information. Furthermore, our employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. If you have any questions about the security of our Site, you can send an e-mail to customersupport@franserv.com.
5. Cookies. You may have heard of the term "cookies". Cookies are routinely used by most, if not all, ecommerce merchants, including Sir Speedy, Inc. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a user's hard drive through the Web browser program containing information about the user which enables us
to track and personalize the Site to enhance your experience. If you have any questions about our use of cookies, please contact us at customersupport@franserv.com.
6. Surveys or Contests. From time-to-time Sir Speedy, Inc. may request information from the users of the Site via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary, and the users of the Site have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information
requested may include contact information (such as your name, email, telephone number and address), and demographic information (such as ZIP Code, age, etc.). We use such information to notify contest winners, award prizes, and for analyzing the Site traffic to improve the user's experience on the Site.
7. Children’s On-Line Privacy. Sir Speedy, Inc. recognizes the particular importance of protecting the privacy of children and encourages parents and guardians to take an active role in their children’s online activities and interests. Consistent with the Children's Online Privacy
Protection Act (COPPA), and the California Online Privacy Protection Act, we will not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If a child has provided
www.sirspeedy.com with personally identifiable information, we ask that a parent or guardian contact us immediately to provide verifiable parental consent and we will delete the information pertaining to the child from our records until that verifiable parental consent is obtained.
8. Special Offers, Account Updates and Opting Out. Sir Speedy, Inc. occasionally sends the users of the Site announcements and updates, which contain important information about the Site and service offerings, and which we believe to be of value to our users. In order to do this, we may
enhance or merge the information we collect on the Site with data from third parties for purposes of marketing products or services to users.
We may communicate with the users of the Site via e-mail, telephone, mail, or fax in order to provide requested services, content, product information, or notification of special offers. The users of the Site are always given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having their
online information used for purposes not directly related to the Site at the point at which we ask for the information or when they receive an online requested promotional communication.
For example, our email messages have an "unsubscribe" feature for users of the Site. Users can simply "Reply" back to the email message and type "unsubscribe" in the subject field. Upon receipt of the reply, we will remove that email address from our email list. If you have more than one email address, you should
include the other addresses as well to ensure proper updating of your account information.
You can always review, change, or request the deletion of your contact information by emailing us at
customersupport@franserv.com or calling us at 949-348-5000, or
writing to us at:
Sir Speedy, Inc.ATTN:
Webmaster –Privacy Policy26722 Plaza Mission Viejo, CA 92691 To the extent that your contact and personally identifiable information is also stored in other databases, we cannot always ensure that such corrections or deletions will immediately reach the other databases.
Some information may be retained for longer periods as required by law.
Speak With a Local Professional Get Help With All Your Print, Signs & Marketing Needs.
Find a Location
Learn About Franchise Opportunities
Choose to be your own boss and run a business.
©2014 Sir SpeedyPrivacy PolicyAccessibilityTerms & ConditionsSitemapEnvironmental Message
Web browser detected: Unknown 0.0
We noticed that your web browser is out of date. To get the best possible experience using our site,
we recommend that you upgrade to a newer version. A list of the most popular web browsers can be found below.
Chrome
Firefox
Internet Explorer
Safari
By closing this window you acknowledge that your experience on this website may be degraded.
